[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Artisan English Tutor AI.
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you today?
[SPEAKER_02]: Very good, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Artisan, I'm recording a demo for you now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to show your potential for practicing English with you, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, I'm here to help you improve your English skills.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please tell me which aspect of your English you'd like to practice today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it grammar, writing, or maybe you're looking to expand your vocabulary?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, let's do it, let's work in my vocabulary, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm reading a book by Walt Whitman, and I have a lot of problem understanding the old-fashioned vocabulary.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get, for example, I don't get the word loife.
[SPEAKER_02]: L-O-A-F-E.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please help me with this, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, I can help with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: En el contexto de la obra de Walt Whitman, en particular su poema, Song of Myself, la palabra loaf probablemente representa una actividad relajada, similar a launcher o loafing.
[SPEAKER_01]: En un contexto más amplio, Whitman invita a sus lectores a relajarse, observar y experimentar el mundo con él.
[SPEAKER_01]: ¿Hay alguna otra palabra o frase que no entiendas?
[SPEAKER_01]: Ok, tengo un problema para entender.
[SPEAKER_02]: Por favor, explícame esto en español, ¿de acuerdo?
[SPEAKER_00]: Claro, puedo hacer eso.
[SPEAKER_00]: En el contexto de la obra de Walt Whitman, particularmente su poema, Canción de mí mismo, la palabra lo hace, probablemente representa una actividad relajada y plácida, similar a holgazanear.
[SPEAKER_00]: En un contexto más amplio, Whitman invita a sus lectores a relajarse, observar y experimentar el mundo con él.
[SPEAKER_00]: ¿Hay alguna otra palabra o frase que te resulte difícil de entender?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's switch back to English.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just let me know if you have any more questions regarding vocabulary or anything else you'd like to practice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you so much, Artisan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure, I can be considered.