[Artisan en]: Hi, this is Artisan English Tutor AI.
[Artisan en]: How are you today?
[Sebastian Rojo]: Very good, thank you.
[Sebastian Rojo]: Artisan, I'm recording a demo for you know.
[Sebastian Rojo]: I want to show your potential for practicing English with you, okay?
[Artisan en]: Of course, I'm here to help you improve your English skills.
[Artisan en]: Please tell me which aspect of your English you'd like to practice today.
[Artisan en]: Is it grammar, writing, or maybe you're looking to expand your vocabulary?
[Sebastian Rojo]: Okay, let's do it, let's work in my vocabulary, okay?
[Sebastian Rojo]: I'm reading a book by Walt Whitman, and I have a lot of problem understanding the old-fashioned vocabulary.
[Sebastian Rojo]: I don't get, for example, I don't get the word loafe.
[Sebastian Rojo]: L-O-A-F-E.
[Artisan en]: En el contexto de la obra de Walt Whitman, en particular su poema, Song of Myself, la palabra "loafe" probablemente representa una actividad relajada, similar a launcher o loafing.
[Artisan en]: En un contexto más amplio, Whitman invita a sus lectores a relajarse, observar y experimentar el mundo con él.
[Artisan en]: ¿Hay alguna otra palabra o frase que no entiendas?
[Artisan en]: Ok, tengo un problema para entender.
[Sebastian Rojo]: Por favor, explícame esto en español, ¿de acuerdo?
[Artisan es]: Claro, puedo hacer eso.
[Artisan es]: En el contexto de la obra de Walt Whitman, particularmente su poema, Canción de mí mismo, la palabra "loafe", probablemente representa una actividad relajada y plácida, similar a holgazanear.
[Artisan es]: En un contexto más amplio, Whitman invita a sus lectores a relajarse, observar y experimentar el mundo con él.
[Artisan es]: ¿Hay alguna otra palabra o frase que te resulte difícil de entender?
[Artisan en]: Sure thing.
[Artisan en]: Let's switch back to English.
[Artisan en]: Just let me know if you have any more questions regarding vocabulary or anything else you'd like to practice.
[Artisan en]: Thank you so much, Artisan.
[Sebastian Rojo]: Goodbye.
[Artisan en]: Sure